<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anxiety on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/tags/anxiety/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anxiety on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/tags/anxiety/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Driving Win-Set</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/driving/</guid>
      <description>Driving Win-Set I think there are many dimensions to win-sets. I&amp;rsquo;ll write them below
What Do I Want What are my goals? What do I want from a situation.. that is bound in time and context?
While driving what do I really want?
 I do not want impact anyting I do not want to hit others I do not want a ticket I want to minimize damage to my car I want to drive efficiently  How do I accomplish these things This is harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win-Sets</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/win-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/win-sets/</guid>
      <description>Win-Sets I read a paper in university about the way institutions make decisions&amp;hellip; Or should I say the people wihtin an institution make decisions. I have applied it to analysis, but not my actual life. I&amp;rsquo;m going to try that now.
Background A decision is made when all parties responsible for making a decision permit a decision to be made. The author I think posed this as when it is in the perceived interest of the legitimate decision maker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Matters</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/todo_es_sacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/todo_es_sacre/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing this I think that everything&amp;hellip; literally every detail is important.
Everything Matters I do not know if this a radical idea. From my experience, I recall people saying to me&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;it is fine&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it is good enough&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; I disagree. To me, every individual detail matters. The context of a situation or the state of an environment at any given state in time influences my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Cigarettes... Again</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/cigarettes_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/cigarettes_again/</guid>
      <description>Smoking Cigarettes&amp;hellip; Again Yesterday I wrote about smoking cigarettes and going out. I had told myself I was over it&amp;hellip;.
A Date Before I Leave Town I had coffee with someone that I am interested before taking off on a road trip to Colorado. At the root of it I think I am attracted to her. I can come up with a number of reasons why.. but I do not really know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embrace Mundanity</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/embrace_mundanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/embrace_mundanity/</guid>
      <description>Why Life is hard enough. Do not chase glory.
What do I mean Life is hard enough. Every single act within my daily life is incredibly difficult. I am nearly 30 years old and still have to force myself to brush my teath every day, to shower, to eat a few square meals a day. These little daily tasks that are truly important to our health and wellbeing are by far the most difficult and sometimes the least prioritized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Cigarettes</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/cigarettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/cigarettes/</guid>
      <description>Smoking Cigarettes I used to smoke when I went out with friends. That was years ago. I left that behind me as one of those things I did in college.
Tonight I went out with someone I met recently at a cafe. A friend of a friend. We had an okay time, but I did not feel the chemistry I had hoped for. We went to a restaurant that was okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entering my Car</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/enter_my_car/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/enter_my_car/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing this I am trying to approach life from the perspective that every action throughout the day&amp;hellip; no matter how mundane&amp;hellip; defines in some way my character. Each little action can either make life easier or more difficult for me. I do not know if it is possible for an action to be completely neutral.. I am thinking that through.
Entering my car How do I currently enter my car?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
