<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Databases on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/en/tags/databases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Databases on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</webMaster>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:55:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/en/tags/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Postgres to Neo4j Workflow: Relationships</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/supreme-court-meta-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:10:02 -0500</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/supreme-court-meta-relationships/</guid>
      <description>Updating the PostGres to Neo workflow with Standard Meta Data Relationships In my previous post i detailed how to export data from postgresql to neo4j with a java workflow.. but I did not add how add relationships once the node insert completes.&#xA;Here is the repo btw https://github.com/justin-napolitano/supreme-court-transfer&#xA;RelationshipCreator.java package com.supreme_court_transfer; import org.neo4j.driver.Session; import org.neo4j.driver.Transaction; import org.neo4j.driver.TransactionWork; import org.slf4j.Logger; import org.slf4j.LoggerFactory; public class RelationshipCreator { private static final Logger logger = LoggerFactory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postgres to Neo4j Workflow</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/supreme-court-to-postgres-to-neo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:10:02 -0500</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/supreme-court-to-postgres-to-neo/</guid>
      <description>Streamlining Data Transfer from PostgreSQL to Neo4j with Java In my previous few posts I put together a postgres db of supreme court meta data. That is cool. I have a few more ideas.. but I wanted to explore the graph a bit before expanding it with some nlp. So in this post I am writing about how to ingest a bunch of nodes into neo4j with a java workflow. In the next post I&amp;rsquo;ll detail adding relationships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERN Stack with GraphQl and Apollo</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/sup-court-pern-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:16:27 -0500</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/sup-court-pern-stack/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up a PERN Stack with GraphQL and Apollo: Source Repo : https://github.com/justin-napolitano/sup-court-pern-stack.git&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with a knowledge graph recently. Most of the data modelling is complete&amp;hellip; well at least the groundwork is done.&#xA;In this part of the series,we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of setting up a PostgreSQL, Express, React, Node.js (PERN) stack application with GraphQL and Apollo.&#xA;The point is to build out a backend so I can then build out a react client to explore the beautiful grapth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Hugo XML Output for RSS Feed</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/hugo-rss-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/hugo-rss-setup/</guid>
      <description>Why I have a mysql db that will be used to store values read from the rss feed of my hugo site. I need some add some keys to help with organization&#xA;Parts of this series part 1 part 2 part 3 part 4 Resources Hugo Page Resources Hugo Page Params Hugo RSS Templates RSS Config Copy over the posts/rss.xml file from your theme From hugo root you would do something like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install MySQL Server on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</guid>
      <description>Why I am working on an autoposting tool for social sites. in order to complete that i want a db to log the metadata of my posts Parts of this series part 1 part 2 MYSQL Resources APT install guide MYSQL config guide Post Install configuration Install Download the config files go to this link and download the script.&#xA;https://dev.mysql.com/downloads/repo/apt/&#xA;Install the release package with dpkg note that the w.x.y.z will change according to the release package</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure mysql server on ubuntu</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/mysql-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/en/posts/mysql-config/</guid>
      <description>Why I installed mysql in the previous post. Now I need to setup users, create a db, and create a table.&#xA;Parts of this series part 1 part 2 part 3 MYSQL Resources APT install guide MYSQL config guide Create a new user Login as Root mysql -u root -p Create some users In my case I will create 4 users accounts.&#xA;Cobra@localhost Cobra@jnapolitano.com admin@localhost dummy@localhost dummy is just used to test service connection and has not access grants or writes</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
