<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>procedures on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/categories/procedures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in procedures on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/categories/procedures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Giving Up</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/giving-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/giving-up/</guid>
      <description>Giving Up There are a lot of things that I do not want to do. I do them still. I do not entirely know why. I want to give them up.
Food There is much food that I find disgusting&amp;hellip;Yet I eat it because well I need to eat.. or I&amp;rsquo;m with people that want to eat certain foods.
Street Food So this trend of eating at taco trucks or food trucks was fun to follow along with years ago&amp;hellip; but I am tired of getting sick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving Win-Set</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/driving/</guid>
      <description>Driving Win-Set I think there are many dimensions to win-sets. I&amp;rsquo;ll write them below
What Do I Want What are my goals? What do I want from a situation.. that is bound in time and context?
While driving what do I really want?
 I do not want impact anyting I do not want to hit others I do not want a ticket I want to minimize damage to my car I want to drive efficiently  How do I accomplish these things This is harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embrace Mundanity</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/embrace_mundanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/embrace_mundanity/</guid>
      <description>Why Life is hard enough. Do not chase glory.
What do I mean Life is hard enough. Every single act within my daily life is incredibly difficult. I am nearly 30 years old and still have to force myself to brush my teath every day, to shower, to eat a few square meals a day. These little daily tasks that are truly important to our health and wellbeing are by far the most difficult and sometimes the least prioritized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entering my Car</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/enter_my_car/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/enter_my_car/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing this I am trying to approach life from the perspective that every action throughout the day&amp;hellip; no matter how mundane&amp;hellip; defines in some way my character. Each little action can either make life easier or more difficult for me. I do not know if it is possible for an action to be completely neutral.. I am thinking that through.
Entering my car How do I currently enter my car?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
