<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflection on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/categories/reflection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflection on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/categories/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bad Food</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/bad-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/bad-food/</guid>
      <description>Bad Food I am letting go of bad food.
Bad food to me is
 Unhealthy Harmful to my teeth Meat (I will expand) Overly expensive Ornamental Idolized  Unhealthy I do not really know what is unhealthy.. I think many things in moderation are probably okay.. That said I know that I want to avoid excess
 Salt Sugar Saturated Fat Calories  So what do I actually eat now that I find unhealthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Games</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/video-games/</guid>
      <description>Video Games I am letting go of video games.
Binge I binge two games annually.. Crusader Kings (whatver iteration is latest) and Europa Universalis 4. I find maybe twice a year where I play one or the other until I burn out.. Typically about 30 hours..
This year I have also played about half of fallout 3 and equally as much of fallout 4.
Lonliness Playing games makes me feel horribly lonely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instragram</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/instagram/</guid>
      <description>Instagram I cannot help myself from abuse instagram. I tried&amp;hellip; I want to connect with friends&amp;hellip; but it is too addicting
Scrolling It is near impossible not to scroll. I try to catch up with my friends. I scroll. I feel sad.
Connection I want to connect.. Instagram can facillitate that.. However, these are often shallow connections. That might be okay, but if I want more than a quick rush&amp;hellip; I need to make the effort to connect in person.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
