<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflection on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/categories/reflection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflection on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/categories/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love is Hard</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/love-is-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/love-is-hard/</guid>
      <description>To Will The Good In The Other I watched a youtube video once about &amp;ldquo;what is love?&amp;rdquo;. I listened to a Roman Catholic Bishop discuss St. Thomas Acquinas&#39; understanding of love. To will the good in the other.. to let go of oneself in order to will for good in the person that one loves. This is hard.
Love is Hard I am living through one of those periods in my life where I have to overcome myself in order to meet the demands of reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Matters</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/todo_es_sacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/todo_es_sacre/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing this I think that everything&amp;hellip; literally every detail is important.
Everything Matters I do not know if this a radical idea. From my experience, I recall people saying to me&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;it is fine&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;it is good enough&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; I disagree. To me, every individual detail matters. The context of a situation or the state of an environment at any given state in time influences my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating Raising Canes</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/raising_canes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/raising_canes/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing this Tonight, I mistreated my body. I had raising Canes. I feel disgusting.
Food review I tried the combo box - a massive amount of french fries served with coleslaw, some bread, and some chicken tenders.
The Fries They were fries - the crinkle cut variety- fried up in old grease. They tasted like typical fries, but the oil was so old that the fries tasted like the grease underneath the lunch room tables you&amp;rsquo;d find a public high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overtrain</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/overtrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/overtrain/</guid>
      <description>Why i like to exercise. i like to over-exercise. i do not listen to my body when it needs rest. i feel as if more movement is more better.
i am getting older. i do not recover quickly.
Running when i feel stressed i run. it is a low cost way to move.
Running too far when i run, i feel a need to prove to myself that i am a runner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
