<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>git on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/tags/git/</link>
    <description>Recent content in git on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/tags/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Build and Deploy GH Workflow</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/gh-pages-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/gh-pages-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Creating a GH Workflow to Build and Deploy a hugo site to gh-pages Why To simplify the build process.
Creating the Workflow create your yaml config file touch hugo.yaml Set the trigger and the environment defaults The code below creates a trigger on push from the main and the gh-pages branches. It also sets read and write permissions to permit executing code and building hugo.
on:# Runs on pushes targeting the default branchpush:branches:- main# - pit# - ghpages- gh-pages# Allows you to run this workflow manually from the Actions tabworkflow_dispatch:# Sets permissions of the GITHUB_TOKEN to allow deployment to GitHub Pagespermissions:contents:readpages:writeid-token:write# Allow only one concurrent deployment, skipping runs queued between the run in-progress and latest queued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCP Cloud Run Job Scraper</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/loc_scraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/loc_scraper/</guid>
      <description>Library of Congress Scraper Job This repo scrapes the library of congress for all of the US Supreme Court Cases available on their platform. I intent to use this data to create a research tool to better understand the corpus of text.
Quick History of this project I had started work on this as an undergraduate at university, but the chatbot apis were not yet available.. and training modesl were far too expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a GCP Client Tool</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/gcputils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/gcputils/</guid>
      <description>Creating a GCP Client Tool in Python Why I often find myself reuuing the same bits of code when working with GCP. It is very important to avoid creating multiple development trees of the same classes. I have done this before for large projects. It will lead to a very difficult to maintain stack of tools that will spaghettify over time.
Creating the submodule Create an empty directory mkdir gcpuptils Add the following code to a gcpclient.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
