<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fail on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/tags/fail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fail on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:24:58 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/tags/fail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automate Posting Hugo Blog to Social Sites (with a db)</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-rss-mysql-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:24:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-rss-mysql-update/</guid>
      <description>Background In the previous few posts I detailed my progress in automating a site. I am going about this by using an rss scraper to post new posts to social.
I had initally thought about doing this really naively, but I want a database. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel right without using one. I am somewhat upset with myself, because I am basically just recreating wordpress&amp;hellip; but so it goes.
Previous posts in this series  part 1 part 2 part 3 part 4 part 5  Expand a previous script In a previous post I wrote about how to scan an rss feed on my personal site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate Posting Hugo Blog to Social Sites...Second Attempt</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/python-rss-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 22:36:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/python-rss-reader/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on This Second Pass  I will create a script that parses the sites rss feed&amp;hellip; it will then traverse the xml tree entries&amp;hellip; if a date is newer than the last publish date&amp;hellip; publish that post&amp;hellip;  I am still thinking through how to publish. I will likely write a monolithic script here, but ideally I would write an api or a batch processor to handle this in some way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate Posting Hugo Blog to Social Sites... Failure</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-social-publisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-social-publisher/</guid>
      <description>Why I have a hugo blog that is a pian to share across my social feeds. I want to automate it.
Create a mockup For this I quickly sketched out my thoughts onto a writing pad. My thinking is that I will drop a yaml file into each post directory to be read by a a python application calling social apis.
Mockup As you can see this is very rudimentary. I will traverse the posts directories looking for a publish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
