<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>databases on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/tags/databases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in databases on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:36:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/tags/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure Hugo XML Output for RSS Feed</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-rss-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:36:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/hugo-rss-setup/</guid>
      <description>Why I have a mysql db that will be used to store values read from the rss feed of my hugo site. I need some add some keys to help with organization
Parts of this series  part 1 part 2 part 3 part 4  Resources  Hugo Page Resources Hugo Page Params Hugo RSS Templates  RSS Config Copy over the posts/rss.xml file from your theme From hugo root you would do something like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure mysql server on ubuntu</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:20:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-config/</guid>
      <description>Why I installed mysql in the previous post. Now I need to setup users, create a db, and create a table.
Parts of this series  part 1 part 2 part 3  MYSQL Resources  APT install guide MYSQL config guide  Create a new user Login as Root mysql -u root -p Create some users In my case I will create 4 users accounts.
 Cobra@localhost Cobra@jnapolitano.com admin@localhost dummy@localhost  dummy is just used to test service connection and has not access grants or writes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install MySQL Server on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:20:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</guid>
      <description>Why  I am working on an autoposting tool for social sites. in order to complete that i want a db to log the metadata of my posts  Parts of this series  part 1 part 2  MYSQL Resources  APT install guide MYSQL config guide Post Install configuration  Install Download the config files go to this link and download the script.
https://dev.mysql.com/downloads/repo/apt/
Install the release package with dpkg  note that the w.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
