<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bash on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>jnapolitano.com/tags/bash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bash on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>jayburdindustries</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:23:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jnapolitano.com/tags/bash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sync Gh Submodules Across a Super Project</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/gh_submodule_sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:23:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/gh_submodule_sync/</guid>
      <description>Overview This script is designed to initialize and update all submodules in a GitHub repository to the latest commits from their respective remote repositories. It ensures that all submodules, including nested submodules, are synchronized with their remote counterparts.
Prerequisites  Ensure that you have Git installed on your system. Ensure that you have cloned the repository containing the submodules.  Usage  Save the script to a file, for example, sync_submodules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Store Useful Github Scripts</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/github_scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:19:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/github_scripts/</guid>
      <description>Overview The github-scripts repository is a collection of useful scripts for managing and automating tasks in GitHub repositories. Each script is maintained as a submodule, allowing for modular management and easy updates.
Table of Contents  Overview Repository Structure Submodules  Sync Submodules Script Add Your Submodule Here   How to Use Contributing License  Repository Structure github-scripts/ ├── sync-submodules-script/ # Submodule for syncing Git submodules │ ├── sync_submodules.sh # Bash script to sync submodules │ └── README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install MySQL Server on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:20:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/mysql-install-buntu/</guid>
      <description>Why  I am working on an autoposting tool for social sites. in order to complete that i want a db to log the metadata of my posts  Parts of this series  part 1 part 2  MYSQL Resources  APT install guide MYSQL config guide Post Install configuration  Install Download the config files go to this link and download the script.
https://dev.mysql.com/downloads/repo/apt/
Install the release package with dpkg  note that the w.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCP Cloud Run Job Scraper</title>
      <link>jnapolitano.com/posts/loc_scraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jnapolitano.com/posts/loc_scraper/</guid>
      <description>Library of Congress Scraper Job This repo scrapes the library of congress for all of the US Supreme Court Cases available on their platform. I intent to use this data to create a research tool to better understand the corpus of text.
Quick History of this project I had started work on this as an undergraduate at university, but the chatbot apis were not yet available.. and training modesl were far too expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
