<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Git on Justin Napolitano</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/tags/git/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Git on Justin Napolitano</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</webMaster>
    <copyright>COBRACORP</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:15:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/tags/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GCP Cloud Run: LOC Flattener</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/posts/loc_normalizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/posts/loc_normalizer/</guid>
      <description>Library of Congress Normalizer Job This repo normalizes the existing library of congress schema into a db that wil then be used to construct a knowledge graph of supreme court law.&#xA;Plan Setup a venv to run locally Install requirements Write out the script to interface with gcp Set up a docker container and test locally build the image upload to gcp create the job Setup the venv Install I installed virtualenv locally on ubuntu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Build and Deploy GH Workflow</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/posts/gh-pages-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/posts/gh-pages-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Creating a GH Workflow to Build and Deploy a hugo site to gh-pages Why To simplify the build process.&#xA;Creating the Workflow create your yaml config file touch hugo.yaml Set the trigger and the environment defaults The code below creates a trigger on push from the main and the gh-pages branches. It also sets read and write permissions to permit executing code and building hugo.&#xA;on: # Runs on pushes targeting the default branch push: branches: - main # - pit # - ghpages - gh-pages # Allows you to run this workflow manually from the Actions tab workflow_dispatch: # Sets permissions of the GITHUB_TOKEN to allow deployment to GitHub Pages permissions: contents: read pages: write id-token: write # Allow only one concurrent deployment, skipping runs queued between the run in-progress and latest queued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCP Cloud Run Job Scraper</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/posts/l_o_c_scraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>personal.jnapolitano@gmail.com (Justin Napolitano)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/posts/l_o_c_scraper/</guid>
      <description>Library of Congress Scraper Job This repo scrapes the library of congress for all of the US Supreme Court Cases available on their platform. I intent to use this data to create a research tool to better understand the corpus of text.&#xA;Quick History of this project I had started work on this as an undergraduate at university, but the chatbot apis were not yet available.. and training modesl were far too expensive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
